<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Titou Coch</title>
    <link>https://titoucoch.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Titou Coch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 19:20:33 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://titoucoch.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sport-Track Web Site</title>
      <link>https://titoucoch.github.io/projects/sport_track/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 19:20:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://titoucoch.github.io/projects/sport_track/</guid>
      <description>Sport-Track, web application that will revolutionize amateur sports Created to facilitate the management of sports teams, the application will help thousands of licensed players throughout the country to access useful information such as the training session and game schedules but also statistics and messages from the team and staff. For messaging we used a web socket to make it dynamic. We used the ratchet library which allows instantiating a web socket server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encoder, Scanner</title>
      <link>https://titoucoch.github.io/projects/encoder_scanner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 20:04:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://titoucoch.github.io/projects/encoder_scanner/</guid>
      <description>Encoding information into a bar code and Scanner : In this project I developed an encoder to encode an amateur sportsman’s license in bar code form. After studying the different bar codes that exist and I chose to create a bar code in height and not in width. Especially inspired by the spotify code.
For encoding : I start with information that is a string of ten characters which includes uppercase letters, miniscule letters and numbers .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Representation</title>
      <link>https://titoucoch.github.io/projects/representation_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 14:04:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://titoucoch.github.io/projects/representation_data/</guid>
      <description>Represent complex data on a Heat Map Simple application to visualize road accidents in the city of Lille. I recovered an open source database of past road accidents with conditions. Accident Database : Table Data Example Cause Intersection, Passing, Parking, Drunkenness&amp;hellip; Date 1985-01-07 18:10:00, 1999-10-10 17:10:00, 1998-02-25 06:55:00&amp;hellip; Condition Moist, Wet, Freezing, Snow cover, Muddy Fat&amp;hellip; Involved Bicycle, Bus, Light car, truck, Pedestrian minus 10 years&amp;hellip; Weather Fair weather, Heavy rain, Snow, Strong storm wind, Mist&amp;hellip; Location Latitude (10430), Longitude(10430)&amp;hellip; Brightness Half day, Light night, Insufficient night light, Night without lighting&amp;hellip; Risk Normal, Dangerous, Very Dangerous&amp;hellip; Involvement Human, Two wheels, Vehicle, Other reason&amp;hellip; I connect to the database using the python library named pymysql import pymysql conn = pymysql.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graph Path</title>
      <link>https://titoucoch.github.io/projects/graph_path/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:12:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://titoucoch.github.io/projects/graph_path/</guid>
      <description>Apply multiple algorithms on graphs Grap : The graph is composed of the 465 bus stop GPS coordinates of the BAB (Biaritz, Anglet, Bayonne) region in France Development I have developed a graph traversal application using Python and the libraries Tkinter and Graphics. The application applies various well-known algorithms such as A*, Dijkstra, Floyd-Warshall, and Bellman-Ford on a bus stop map. The application features a menu and a graphical map where the results can be observed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
